<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<catalog>
    <book id="0001">
        <title>Three Little Pigs</title>
        <rating>4.21</rating>
        <totalRatings>27569</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>17174</bestSellerRank>
        <author>Random House Disney</author>
        <publisher>Random House USA Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>The three little pigs have never looked so cute and the big bad wolf never looked so bad in this retelling of the classic fairy tale! Vintage Disney artwork from the 1940s makes this book an important addition to every Little Golden Book collector s library."</description>
        <year>2005</year> 
        <date>11 Jan 2005</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0002">
        <title>The Little Prince</title>
        <rating>4.3</rating>
        <totalRatings>1352753</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>315</bestSellerRank>
        <author>Antoine de Saint-Exupery</author>
        <publisher>Wordsworth Editions Ltd</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>Translated by Irene Testot-Ferry.
The Little Prince is a classic tale of equal appeal to children and adults. On one level it is the story of an airman's discovery, in the desert, of a small boy from another planet - the Little Prince of the title - and his stories of intergalactic travel, while on the other hand it is a thought-provoking allegory of the human condition.
First published in 1943, the year before the author's death in action, this translation contains Saint-Exupery's delightful illustrations.</description>
    <year>1998</year> 
    <date>01 Jan 1998</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0003">
        <title>Goodnight Moon</title>
        <rating>4.28</rating>
        <totalRatings>294461</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>77</bestSellerRank>
        <author>Margaret Wise Brown</author>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>In a great green room, tucked away in bed, is a little bunny. Goodnight room, goodnight moon. And to all the familiar things in the softly lit room--to the picture of the three little bears sitting on chairs, to the clocks and his socks, to the mittens and the kittens, to everything one by one--the little bunny says goodnight.
In this classic of children's literature, beloved by generations of readers and listeners, the quiet poetry of the words and the gentle, lulling illustrations combine to make a perfect book for the end of the day.
This board book edition is the perfect size for little hands.</description>
    <year>2011</year>    
    <date>24 Jun 2011</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0004">
        <title>Charlotte's Web</title>
        <rating>4.17</rating>
        <totalRatings>1346447</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>859</bestSellerRank>
        <author>E B White</author>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>This beloved book by E. B. White, author of Stuart Little and The Trumpet of the Swan, is a classic of children's literature that is just about perfect. This paperback edition includes a foreword by two-time Newbery winning author Kate DiCamillo.Some Pig. Humble. Radiant. These are the words in Charlotte's Web, high up in Zuckerman's barn. Charlotte's spiderweb tells of her feelings for a little pig named Wilbur, who simply wants a friend. They also express the love of a girl named Fern, who saved Wilbur's life when he was born the runt of his litter.</description>
    <year>2012</year>    
    <date>10 Apr 2012</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0005">
        <title>Stuart Little</title>
        <rating>3.89</rating>
        <totalRatings>104158</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>7398</bestSellerRank>
        <author>E B White</author>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>Stuart Little is no ordinary mouse. Born to a family of humans, he lives in New York City with his parents, his older brother George, and Snowbell the cat. Though he's shy and thoughtful, he's also a true lover of adventure.
Stuart's greatest adventure comes when his best friend, a beautiful little bird named Margalo, disappears from her nest. Determined to track her down, Stuart ventures away from home for the very first time in his life. He finds adventure aplenty. But will he find his friend?</description>
    <year>2020</year>    
    <date>01 Sep 2020</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0006">
        <title>Matilda</title>
        <rating>4.31</rating>
        <totalRatings>576958</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>668</bestSellerRank>
        <author>Roald Dahl</author>
        <publisher>Penguin Putnam Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>From the bestselling author of Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and The BFG! Matilda is a sweet, exceptional young girl, but her parents think she's just a nuisance. She expects school to be different but there she has to face Miss Trunchbull, a kid-hating terror of a headmistress. When Matilda is attacked by the Trunchbull she suddenly discovers she has a remarkable power with which to fight back. It'll take a superhuman genius to give Miss Trunchbull what she deserves and Matilda may be just the one to do it!</description>
    <year>2007</year>    
    <date>16 Aug 2007</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0007">
        <title>The Trumpet of the Swan</title>
        <rating>4.08</rating>
        <totalRatings>67370</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>16107</bestSellerRank>
        <author>E B White</author>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>Like the rest of his family, Louis is a trumpeter swan. But unlike his four brothers and sisters, Louis can't trumpet joyfully. In fact, he can't even make a sound. And since he can't trumpet his love, the beautiful swan Serena pays absolutely no attention to him.</description>
    <year>2020</year>    
    <date>02 Sep 2020</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0008">
        <title>Classic Starts (R): Peter Pan</title>
        <rating>4.22</rating>
        <totalRatings>953</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>32298</bestSellerRank>
        <author>J. M. Barrie</author>
        <publisher>Sterling Publishing Co Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>"All children grow up. All except one." That special child is Peter Pan, and since making his debut on the stage in 1904, this eternal youth has carried boys and girls off to magical, marvelous Neverland. It's a trip that all kids want to make, and with this easy-to-read version of the classic, everyone can fly "second to the right, and straight on till morning" with Peter. Along with Wendy, John, and Michael Darling, they'll meet the fairy Tinkerbell, the Lost Boys, and the menacing Captain Hook.</description>
    <year>2009</year>    
    <date>03 Mar 2009</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0009">
        <title>The Wind in the Willows</title>
        <rating>3.98</rating>
        <totalRatings>141868</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>4001</bestSellerRank>
        <author>Kenneth Grahame</author>
        <publisher>Wordsworth Editions Ltd</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>Far from fading with time, Kenneth Grahame's classic tale of fantasy has attracted a growing audience in each generation.Rat, Mole, Badger and the preposterous Mr Toad, have brought delight to many through the years with their odd adventures on and by the river, and at the imposing residence of Toad Hall.</description>
    <year>1998</year>    
    <date>01 Jan 1998</date>
    </book>
    <book id="0010">
        <title>Winnie-The-Pooh (Puffin Modern Classics)</title>
        <rating>4.33</rating>
        <totalRatings>268201</totalRatings>
        <bestSellerRank>442</bestSellerRank>
        <author>A.A. Milne</author>
        <publisher>Penguin Putnam Inc</publisher>
        <language>English</language>
        <description>Happy 90th birthday, to one of the world's most beloved icons of children's literature, Winnie-the-Pooh! Since 1926, Winnie-the-Pooh and his friends--Piglet, Owl, Tigger, and the ever doleful Eeyore--have endured as the unforgettable creations of A.A. Milne, who wrote this book for his son, Christopher Robin, and Ernest H. Shepard, who lovingly gave Pooh and his companions shape. These characters and their stories are timeless treasures of childhood that continue to speak to all of us with the kind of freshness and heart that distinguishes true storytelling.</description>
    <year>2006</year>    
    <date>01 Jan 2006</date>
    </book>
</catalog>